那是什么？你知道
What was that ? you know
好吧，就给我一点
okay , just , just give me one little
不，几乎没有人举手
No no hands almost there
好吧，我我要把这个脱了
Okay , i'm i'm gonna take this off
不不不
No , no no
嘿，你说你喜欢惊喜
Hey , you said you like surprises
是的，当我知道它们是什么的时候我就会
Yeah i do when i know what they are
哈，你会喜欢的
Ha , you're gonna love it
承诺
Promise
是的，我已经爱上你了
Yeah , i already love with you
牵起你的手
Take your hand
好了，我们到了
all right here we are
什么该开始，什么该开始
got what should start which should start
他们看不见我们在，别脱了
they can't see hey we're in stop taking it off
现在
now
你在开玩笑吗？
are you kidding
哇，我我都不知道这地方还开着
Wow i i i didn't even know this place was open ye
帮我们弄到了名单
Pulls the favors and got us the list
罗布林之夜哦，哈哈哈
robling night oh ha ha ha h
你确定我穿着得体吗
Wow ui are you sure i'm dressful right
你看起来气色很好
you look like a million bucks
燃烧着燃烧着
and it burns burns
把火圈烧了
burn the ring of fire
他们在做喷泉里的钢尖
Hey doing steel points from the fountain
运气不好，对不起，先生，拜托
it's bad luck , sorry sir come on
这是给你的
Here's to you
谢谢你！
thank you
哦,先生
oh sir
你想要
would you like
你要上来吗？我们坐下一班
Are you coming up we'll take the next one
哦，来吧，我们可以想象
oh come on we can visuit
谢谢
thanks
上升
going up
哦，对不起，它有时会这样
oh excuse me sorry it does that sometimes
关于这家伙的一些有趣的事实
Some fun facts about this guy made out
它高494英尺，重9000多吨
It's four hundred and ninety four feet tall and weighs over nine thousand tons
它是用玻璃制成的钢和钢筋混凝土
It's made of steel and reinforced concrete in glass
更令人印象深刻的是
And even more impressive
整个项目比原计划晚了五个月完成
The entire project was completed five months out of schedul
下了个死
我告诉他们的是幻想
What i tell em fancy
是
Yes
我能为您效劳吗？
May i help you
我们有预约电话
We have a reservation cal
哦，对不起
Oh i'm sorry
但首演之夜已经客满了
But we are already over capacity for opening night
如果您不介意的话，我们无法接待您
We cannot accommodate you if you wouldn't mind just stepping aside
非常感谢，没关系
Thank you so much it's okay
我和杰克谈过了
I worked it up with jake
他今天早上是在这里吗
Is he here like like a relit jake go this morning
非常感谢
Thank you so much
哦，宝贝，来吧，来吧
Oh baby one take take one
当然，你很重要，我甚至可以帮我
Sure you very important man that i maybe even help me
她做的
She does
求你了，你快把我撕碎了
Um please you're tearing me apart
但是我很抱歉。我帮不了你
But i'm sorry . i can't help you
如果不是，如果你在心里
If not if you in mind
哦，充满她的先生
Oh mr full of her
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you
我们为您准备了一张漂亮的桌子
We have a lovely table for you
谢谢你这样做
Thank you for this way
它有一个房间
it's got a barooms are nal
等一下
um wait a few
哦,不
oh no
很好，对吗？
It's good right
哦，不，是什么?
oh no what is
我只是从来没来过这么高的地方
I've just never been this high up befor
这次我很抱歉
I'm so sorry this nic
20颗这样的星星让一切怪异的事物变得完美
Twenty such disai starry for everything weird to be perfec
他
he
这是完美的
It is perfec
因为我和你在一起
Because i'm with you
啊奥卡河
Ah oka
我想我喜欢
u i think i loves 对
嘿，找香槟
Hey look for champagn
这是我最喜欢的跑步方式
that's my favorite kind coming running
你喜欢从蓝色药丸开始
you like to start a pill blue with you
我的头掉下来了
i got a falling up my head
爱将心思没有放
好的，我马上回来
Okay i'll be right back
今天我们浪费了这么多肉
Today we are wasted all this meat
那我就永远不能碰我自己了
then i can never touch me
哦，我要用我的b来感受
oh i got to feel it in my b
我被水怎么办
你就是原因
you're the reason why
你现在可别这么做
don't you do right now
嗨，亲爱的
hi sweetie h
是的，一切都好
Yes everything all right
我很好。谢谢你！
I'm fine . thank you
你怀孕多久了
how far along are you what
不，我不是，我不是
oh no i'm i'm not
爱你
我不太清楚
I don't know exactl
也许一两个月吧
Maybe one or two month
这是个好消息
that's wonderful news
不是吗
isn't it
我还没告诉我男朋友
I haven't told my boyfriend
是的
Yeah
他爱你吗？
Does he love you
是
Yes
那他就不会放手
Then he won't let go
当然谢谢你
Thank you of course
再见
Bye
好了，快结束了
Okay , it's almost over
嘿，你在哪儿
Hey , where are you
好吧
Okay
是的
Yeah
我想是的
I think so
来吧，我们来点压力
come on let's get some pressure
我真的需要
I really need to
你先来
Uh , you go first
好吧
Okay
嗯
Um
我本打算晚餐时做的
I was gonna do this at dinner
但是我们有这样的观点
But things we have this view
嘿
Hey
如果你杀了人，别扔硬币
Don't throw that penny if you kill somebody
哦，我很抱歉。当然，伙计
oh , i'm so sorry . of course , man
Fas
嗯，过去的几年
Um , these past few years
我真是太神奇了
i've been absolutely magical
那是，呃
And that's , uh
这是因为观看的原因
that's because of viewing
我th
i th
我想和你共度余生
I want to spend the rest of my life with you
他的意思是
he mean
与我们
with us
我
i
我喜欢这种世界
I like this kind in the worl
你没有不高兴
You're not upset
你在开玩笑吗，不，这，这，这真是不可思议，真的吗
Are you kidding me no this this is this is incredible really
我们的家人在哪里？
where is our family
哦，是的，哈哈哈
oh oh yes ha ha ha
是不是太紧了？
is it too tight
啊，太完美了
ah it's perfect
他让我们去庆祝吧
he let's go celebrate
来吧，带着见到你的喜悦
Come on down the joy that to see yo
当
when
看着你，耶，耶
to look at you see yeah yeah
看到了吗，宝贝，来吧，来吧
see right now baby come on come on and
有没有无奈在你的承诺
你会
贝贝哭啦再哭啦
现在知道你知道你会让我想要展示
know now you know you'll make me wanna show
Make up up：振作起来
make up cheers up 被 shot on me
今晚稍微温柔一点，你就会让它变得柔和
A little bit soft tonight you make it stotonight
有点小
it's a little st
我将赢得爱
And i will win lov
现在我生活在爱中，我是sh
now i'm living loving i am sh
奔向你这么悲伤
你让我们飞翔
我只能
绝不会下的大师
我的笑笑
敲敲敲敲敲敲敲敲吹到
雨滴不停地落在我的
rain drops keep falling on my
但那在我眼里依然会是
but that is in my eyes will still be
啊！怎么有人偷的吗
快走啊走
回来，回来
get back get back 啊
哎跑怎么也跑
所有人都下楼去
everyone down the stairs
嗯啊嗯啊哈啊哈哈
啊啊啊
我意识到向量乘法很可怕
Well i realize vector multiplication is scary
但不是那个伤疤
But it's not that scar
今天就到这里，我们开始准备下周的期末考试
and that's it for today we start prepping for the final next week
我们需要谈谈
we need to talk
哦，这个梦想主宰着我的生活
Oh , this dream is running my lif
我每天晚上的东西
Mine to every night stuff
天啊，我根本睡不着
God , i'm not getting any sleep
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
我能告诉你一件事吗
Um , can i tell you something
是的
Yeah
怎么了
What's up
所以，我交易她的那个女人
So the , the woman in my trading her
她的名字是伊丽兹
Her name is irriz , right
好吧
Okay
那是我祖母的名字
That was my grandmother's name
我，我，我想我
I uh , i , i think i'm
我梦见她了
I'm dreaming about her
你是认真的吗
Are you serious
是的
Yeah
问题是我根本没见过她
The thing is i never even met her
我都不知道她是不是还活着
I don't even know if she's alive
好吧
Okay
要么回家去问问奶奶的事
Well either go home and find out about grandm
希望能阻止梦
and hope that stops the dreams
或者留在这里，在睡梦中死去
or stay here and die in your sleep for real
因为我会杀了你
Because i will murder you
哈哈
Ha ha
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
是的
Yeah
好吧
Okay
爱你
Love you
让我回家吧
Let me to go home
是的
Yeah
安静地
quietly
嘿，有这个
Hey there's this
嘿，爸爸，回家吧，亲爱的
Hey dad , come home sweetie
我很高兴你能来
I'm so glad you're here
非常感谢，我知道
Thank you so much , i know
啊，见到你真高兴
Ah , so great to see you
谢谢你
Thanks for you
谢谢
Thanks
再见，这是给你的
See you that's for you
抱歉查理之前占用了你的房间
Hey , sorry charley took your room a while ag
我的文件在他房间里
And my files are in his room
所以我给你编了个退出的故事
So i made up the pull out for you
这样可以吗？
Is that okay
是的
Yeah
不，听起来完全没问题
No , that sounds totally fine
嘿
Uh , hey
我们还有那盒妈妈的旧东西吗
Do we still have that box of mom's old stuff
里面有一些照片，像是地址簿
It had , uh , some photos like an address book
里面有电话号码
Phone numbers in it
你为什么想要那个
Uh , why do you want that
哦，没什么大不了的
Oh , it's not a big deal
我只是，我觉得我在这附近看到了
i just , i thought i saw lying around here somewhere
忍受正在发生的事情
Standing what's going on
好吧
Okay
这声音真的很奇怪
This is a sound really , really weird
但我，我得找到妈妈的妈妈。虹膜
But i , uh , i just need to find mom's mom . iris
呃
Uh
好吧
Okay
是的
Yeah
这很奇怪
That is weird
妈妈走后，我几年前就把那些盒子处理掉了
And you know , i got rid of those boxes years ago after mom left
哦，你好，查理
Oh hi charlie
嘿
Hey
嗨，伙计们
Um , hi stuff
你好吗？见到你真高兴
How are you ? it's so nice to see you
是的，当然
Yeah , sure
你去找表兄妹
Uh , you go to the cousins
哇
Whoa
听着，你妹妹刚回来
Now look , your sister just got home
我想。欢喜。事实上，你知道吗
I thought . glad . actually , you know what
我可以，我可以开车送你
I can , i can drive you
我想以多种方式看他们，这很好
I was wanting to see them many ways that's fine
嘿，如果你要去看你的表兄弟
Hey , if you're gonna see your cousins
请不要谈论信用卡
Please don't talk about irristcard
是的
Yeah
没有麻烦
No trouble
好吧
All right
我也爱你幸运
I love you lucky too
炭的
charry
说话，说话
Talk , talk
你能不能，我把你脱了
Can you just , i'll take you out of these
我想和你谈谈
I'm trying to talk to you
你怎么了？
What's your problem
怎么了，你什么都没说
What i , you haven't said anything this entire time
什么
what
的东西
Stuff
你为什么在这里？
Why are you here
我只是假期才回家
I'm only coming home for holidays
我不能告诉你什么
I can't have to tell you something
但你要保证不告诉别人
But you who have to promise not to tell that
你怀孕了吗？
What are you pregnant
不，我没有怀孕，查理，我不知道
No , i'm not pregnant , charlie , i don't know
你为什么要拒绝呢
Why would you even that's no
我想你在上大学
I'm you're in college
你能保证不告诉爸爸吗
Can you just promise me you won't tell dad
为什么我要说这是严重的？查理
Why would i told that it's serious ? charlie
好的，嗯
okay ， um
我是留校察看
i am an academic probation
哈哈哈，住手
Ha ha ha ha stop that
我的成绩没有提高
I don't get my grades up
对我来说，这是一个重要的时刻
Kind of a stop big moment for me
这有点好笑
This is kind of funny
直就是你们的班长很看重我的成绩
Straight is your class president is valutn funi get my grades u
我会失去奖学金的
i will lose my scholarship u
我很抱歉
i was sorry
会发生什么
What happens
我一闭上眼睛就睡不着
I can't sleep every time i close my eyes
我经常做关于艾瑞斯的噩梦
I have this same recurring nightmare about iris
我们的祖母。我不
our grandmother . i don't
我的意思是它一定有意义
I mean it has to mean something
我不知道，我喝酒用的是东西
i don't know i drink with things
昨晚有个热狗店
There's a hot dog eme last nigh
好像热狗需要我一样
Like the hot dog was needing me
是的
Yeah
你只是做点什么吗？你冷静下来
Do you just do something ? you calm down
我会在网上找到这幅画，你是来这里看我的好意的
I will find this faian online that are you here to look under my kindness
去他的，这是等级地图。它是一个RON
Fuck off it's a rank map . it's a ron
我可以再找个搭讪的家伙
I can find pokeup dude again
我想要这个
I want this this pokeup
噢,是的
Oh yeah
嘿,顾
Hey gu
天啊，你得帮我们上厕所
Oh my gosh ake you help us loo
走路的时候注意脚下
And just just watch your feet while you're stepping
是的，是的，当然。我只是我得先和你爸爸谈谈
Yeah , yeah , sure . uh , i just i gotta talk to your dad first
你他妈回家了
It's fucking you doing home
哦,老兄
Oh dude
她在一所学校工作。嘿
She's working at a school . hey
埃里克，欢迎加入我们
Welcome to the club eric
伙计，你到处找过吗
Dude have you looked anywhere
看我
Look i'
哦，但是看看谁在下面
Oh but look who's down here
你好，胡里奥，我的天啊，你好
Hi julio , my gosh hi even
查理·乔，这是我的小女友
Charlie jue there's my little gal meo
所以我们不得不向珍妮求婚
So we had to propose a with jenny girl
她答应了
She said yes
我的天啊，太棒了。好吧
Oh my god , top . okay
等等，谁是珍妮
Wait , who's uh , who's jenny
他是在初级救生员时认识她的
Oh he met her in junior life guards
初级救生员查理，我没有。
Junior life guards charlie , i didn'
我不知道你在做青少年生活之神
I didn't know you're doing junior life gods okay
那你打算穿什么
So what are you gonna wear
我就留着这把黑色激光枪吧
Uh , i just gonna keep this sible no black lazer
但是是的是的
But yeah yeah
但这很有趣
But it's like a fun
但是我喜欢
but i like
Step stephanie。我的天啊
Step stephanie . oh my gosh
嗨蜂蜜
Hi honey
你好朋友
Hi friend
你怎么在这里，呃
How are you here for , uh
没多久，霍华德叔叔就来了
Not long , uh , is is uncle howard around
是的
Yeah
他又上来了
He's up back again
霍华德，斯蒂芬妮，准备好了
Howard , stephanie here come in ready
她有点累了。一切都好吗？
She's like a little tired . does everything okay
哦,doi
Oh doi
看看你
Look at you
过来，过来，亲爱的
Come here , come here , bl sweetie
见到你真是太好了
Oh it's so good to see you
嘿，你饿了吗
Hey , are you hungry
我想太多了
I assume so much
哦，不，实际上，呃
Oh no , actually , uh
我来是想跟你谈谈你妈妈的事
I came here because i wanted to talk to you about your mother
虹膜
Iris
我知道你不喜欢谈论她
I know you don't like to talk about her
没什么可说的
Not much to tell
嘿，孩子们，来吃午饭吧
Hey kids , come on lunch
呃，只是只是我一直我一直在做关于她的噩梦
Uh , it's it's just that i've been i've been having this recurring nightmare about her
哦亲爱的
Oh honey
可能只是压力太大了
It's probably just stressed
你应该试试褪黑素
You should try melatonin
好吧
Okay
但奇怪的是
But , but the weird thing is
我一直梦想着50年前的一个真实的地方
I've been dreaming about a real place from from fifty years ago
就像一家叫天景的餐厅
It was like a restaurant called the sky view
你知道，这是真的，我刚刚告诉你了吗
You know , it is did did i just tell you about it
她说什么她说什么
What he what did she say
她说了什么吗
Did did she say anything
也许也许如果我能跟她谈谈
And maybe maybe if i could talk to her to k
种马在梦想奶奶的月经补助金
Stud is dreaming about grandmas cycle grant
我以为她死了
I thought she was dead
对我们来说她已经死了
Well , she was dead to us
草原爱尔兰骆驼是一个非常不安的女人和一个故事
Steppe irish camel is a very deeply disturbed woman and a story
如果我能跟她谈谈
If i could just talk to her
然后也许也许我想如果这些梦是不符合标准的
Then then maybe maybe i think if these dreams are off step
放下它吧
Just drop it
我不明白
I don't get it
到底发生了什么，这么糟糕的事
What , what happened that was so bad for one thing
她就是你妈妈搞砸一切的原因
She's the reason that your mother so screwed up
怎么啦？听着，我只是不想再谈这个了
What ? look , i just don't want to talk about this anymore
好的，请往前走
Okay , phoward please
我只是想知道
I just need to know
阿来史蒂夫
Loy stevie
我们的父亲去世后
After our father died
虹膜断裂了
Iris just snapped
她她不让我们去上学
She she wouldn't let us go to school
她把我们锁在屋子里
She locked us inside the house
她痴迷于所有可怕的死法
She obsessed about all the horrific ways we could die
最后情况变得很糟糕
And eventually it got so bad
我的意思是太糟糕了
I mean so bad
国家来了
And the state came i
它把我和你妈妈从她身边带走了
And it took your mother and i away from her
但事情并没有就此结束
But it didn't end there
她她跟踪了我们所有人的寄养生活
She she tracked us all through foster care
当孩子们出生时
And when the kids were born
她开始发这个
She started sending this s
满是讣告的可怕信件
horrible letters that were full of obituaries
还有这些令人不安的尸体照片
And these disturbing pictures of dead bodies
我们不得不搬家，这样她就不能再联系我们了
We had to move so she couldn't contact us anymore
所以，呃
So , uh
那些信你还留着吗
Do you still have any of those letters
所以
so
我的史蒂夫
I stevie
听我说
Listen to me
那个女人是个病态的危险人物
That woman is a sick and dangerous person
为了你的幸福和安全
And for your wellbeing in your safety
离他远点
Stay the hell away from he
我相信
i believe
我找到了paco
i found paco
在客厅，对
In the living room right
你知道他是md
You know it's md guy
他们是怎么进去的
how did they get in there
天天这个好美
你听到你叔叔说的了，放手吧
You heard your uncle just let it go
就让它过去吧
Just let it go
你不明白
You don't understan
我的整个人生都因为这个梦而分崩离析
My whole life is falling apart because of this dream
不仅如此，我觉得
And not only that i feel lik
我感觉我快要疯了
i feel like i'm losing my mind please
你是唯一能帮助我的人
You are the only person who can help me
如果我让你和艾瑞斯联系你怎么可能永远不会原谅我
how would would never forgive me if i put you in touch with iris
无论你做什么，千万不要去看餐厅餐桌最下面的抽屉
whatever you do ， do not look in the bottom drawer of the dining room cabant
嗨,嗯
Hi um
我是来见艾瑞斯·坎贝尔的
I'm , i'm here to see iris campbell
你没看到征兆吗
did you not see the signs
嗯，嗯，是的，是的，我做了
Uh , uh , yes , yes i did
但是没有访客
But i no visitors
我是你的孙女
i'm your granddaughter
你亲爱的口袋电话钥匙，一切
Your dear pocket phone keys everything
我并不危险
Well i'm not dangerous
我怕的不是你
it's not you i'm afraid of
u
慢慢来
coming slowly
把门关上
Shut the doo
快快快
quick quick quick
不要动
don't move
我的天啊
Oh my god
真的是你
It really is you
我能在你身上看到你母亲的影子
I can see your mother in you
哈哈
ha ha
嗨，我是我是
Hi i'm i'm
所以停，停，不要动
So stop stop , don't move
除非我告诉你
not until i tell you
你想骗我，是不是
Trying to trick me aren't you
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha h
让我放松警惕
Getting me to let my guard down
哈哈，我知道，但是
ha ha i know but
三个
Three
好吧，我坐，就这样
Okay , i am sit that's it
亲爱的，你妈妈好吗
So how is darling your mom
好吧
Okay
哦，呃，不，我不，我不认识她
Oh uh , no i i don't i don't know she , uh
她在我十岁的时候离开了
She left when i was ten
所以我们我们再也见不到她了哦
so we don't we don't see her anymore oh
但你看到了我的信所以你才来这里，对吧
But you saw my letters that's why you're here , right
否
No
嗯
Um
我就是她
I'm actually her
因为我一直梦想着看到天空
Because i've been dreaming about the sky of view
是的是的
Yeah yeah
过去两个月的每一个晚上
Every single night for the past two months
这是这里面的梦是一样的
It's it's the same dream in it here
你在约会
You're on a date
但接着舞池休息了
But then the dance floor break
然后就发生了爆炸
And and then there's an explosio
然后你就倒下死了
And then you fall and dying
是的
Yeah
是的，每个人都会死
Yeah , everyone dies
这不仅仅是你的梦想
And it wasn't just your dream
这是我多年前看到天空时的预感
It was my premonition years ago at the sky view
我瞥见了未来
I got a glimpse into the futur
看到了死亡的后果
And saw what death was about to do
我本来要做晚餐的
I was gonna do with the dinner
但是我们有这样的观点
But things we have this view
如果你杀了人，别扔硬币
Hey don't throw that penny if you kill somebody
哦，我很抱歉
Oh i'm so sorry
当然
Of course
过去的几年绝对是巨大的
These past few years have been absolutely massical
这都是因为你喜欢
And that's all because of you lik
这不是我的euh
This isn't my euh
不是吗?
is that no
每个人都会死
Everyone's going to die
整个大楼都会倒塌
That the the the whole building is going to come down
你是认真的吗
Are you serious
一分钱打死了地狱女人
The penny kup the hell lady
你可以把你做的地方给我
You can give it to me where you doing it
你他妈有毛病
The fuck is wrong with you
我站起来，你知道你会让我想要继续我的杀戮
I rise , you know you'll make me wanna keep my kill up the smoo gam
Freshtra游戏回来了
freshtra game back it
太好了，看不到
Too much good to see it
不要为了玩而玩
Don't play to play
每个人都需要离开
Everyone need to get of
班级的舞蹈就要结束了
The dance for the class is about to break
所有人现在都得出去
Everyone needs to get out now
等等，不，让所有该死的巡演站下来
Wait no get all the damn tour standing to get off
下车
get off
那晚我救了很多人的命
I saved a lot of lives that night
那些本不该被拯救的生命
Lives that were never meant to be saved
之后他们就关门了
They close the restaurant after that
所以它需要额外的翻新
So it needed additional renovations
但它从未重新开放
But it never reopened
最后他们把它拆掉了
Eventually they tore it down
所以你你阻止了这场灾难
But so you you stop the disaster
是
Yes
死神不喜欢你破坏他的计划
The death doesn't like it when you fuck with his plans
这么多年过去了，他又回来了
So over the years he came bac
他杀了那晚在场的所有人
And he killed everyone who was there that night
包括我的保罗
Including my paul
等等，等一下，对不起
Wait , wait a minute , i'm sorry
你是
Did you
你是说死神回来了
Did you say death came back
他是个无情的混蛋
He's a relentless son of a bitch
不完成任务他是不会罢休的
Won't stop till he finishes the job
但我教会了自己如何预见他的到来
But i taught myself how to see him comin
预测他的一举一动
To anticipate his every move
我已经把他关了好几年了
Been keeping him a bay for years now
现在他害我得了癌症
And now he's got me cancer
哦，相信那狗屁
Oh , uh , believe that shit
对不起
Sorry
两个月前得到了诊断
Got the diagnosis two months ago
等等那是那是我开始做梦的时候
Wait that's that's when i started having my dream
看，这是个征兆
See it's a sign
好的，但是为什么呢？
Okay , but why
为什么我会梦到你所看到的
Why am i dreaming about what you saw
也许我的癌症已经过了我的末期
Maybe my cancer passed my permination
你不是吗？也许这就是命运
Aren't you ? maybe it's fate
疯狂的幽默感
Demented sense of humor
谁知道呢
Who the hell knows
重要的是，当宇宙说话时，你要注意
What matters is that when the universe speaks you pay attention
我看到你了，你他妈的
i see you you fuck
嗯
Um
你在跟谁说话啊
Who who are you talking to death
他以为我因为你在这里而分心了
He thinks i'm distracted because you're here
我得把这本书里的东西都教给你
I have to teach you everything in this boo
这需要一些时间来学习基本知识
That will take some time to learn the basics
所以你得待在这里
So you need to stay here
呆在这里
Stay here
外面的世界太危险了
Outside world is too dangerous
我有二十年没去过那里了
I haven't stepped out there in twenty years
在一年内
In a yea
我们会很安全
We can be safe
看到,
See that
哈哈！是的
Ha ha ! yeah
这是我所有的研究
This is all my research
我毕生的心血
My life's work
听着，我。对不起，我不能。
Look , i'm . i'm sorry i , i can'
我不能待在这里
I can't stay here
我得回学校了
I i have to get back to school
但是你知道。我将。我会回来拜访你的。不，我病了
But you know . i'll . i'll come back and i'll visit . no , i'm sick
我活不了那么久了
I won't be alive that long
你不能走，难道你没看到死亡正在向我们家走来吗
You can't leave don't you see death is coming for our family
你不相信我
You don't believe me
不，我是我我想我想我犯了个错误
No , i am i i think think i made a mistake
我想，我想那可能只是个梦
Um , i think it , i think it was probably just a dream
否。等等，至少把书拿走
No . wait , at least take the book
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie
打开你
斯蒂芬妮，别这样，我很抱歉
Stephanie stop look i'm sorr
我不该来这里的
I shouldn't have come here
这本书是救命稻草
This book is a lifeline
它会告诉你保护我们家庭安全所需要知道的一切
It will show you everything you need to know to keep our family safe
你还是不相信我
you still don't believe me
退一步，为什么
step back why
眼见为实
seeing is believing
她的脸都要炸了
It's stuff her face fully explode
有趣的是，我就这样让她一个人待着
And funny is that like i'm just leave her alone
这是我的坏东西，我只是好奇
it's my bad stuff , i'm just curious
关于eteripi你是对的
You were right about eteripi
不，我不应该去那里
Never i never should have went there
亲爱的没必要道歉
Honey was no need to apologize
我很抱歉让你经历这些
I'm so sorry you had to go through that
她死前对我说了些话
She said something to me before she died
她说她的家人要死了
She said death was coming for her family
这很疯狂，对吧
That's it's crazy right
我的天啊
Oh my god
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it
我在这里发邮件，我只是不喜欢你的出现，来吧
i email here i just didn't taste your show up by come on
,嗯
that um
演示
demo
是的
yeah
真的离开
really leave
哇
wow
我们可以回来
We can come back
我觉得你很可笑。快点，下来，过来
i thought you're ridiculous . come on get down here come here
我想她会来烧烤的
think she'll come to the barbecue
腰带
Sash
她要去霍华德叔叔家，我就不去了
Hey , she's going in uncle howard's house then i'm not
你可以搭爸爸的车
You can get a ride with dad
呃
Uh
我觉得你应该和她谈谈
I think you're gonna talk to her
来吧
Come on
你不像我这么记得她
You don't remember her like i do
给她一个机会
Just give her a chance
为什么
Why
查理
Charlie
她抛弃了我们，现在
She abandoned us and now
这么多年过去了，现在她又来了
And now she rolls in here after all these year
还想装作什么都没发生
And wants to act like nothing happened
因为谁会这么做呢
Because who would do that right
等等，什么？我认为
Wait , what ? i think
否
No
这跟我有什么关系
What's that supposed to me
我给你打了很多次电话都没有
I tried calling you so many times and nothing
茱莉亚也一样曾经是最好的朋友
Same with julia used to be best friends
你都不说话了
You don't even talk anymore
好吧
Okay
我。我。我。对不起，我。
I'm . i'm . i'm . sorry , i
过去几个月我一直在分心，因为这个就在那里
I've just been distracted the last couple of months because this is right there
但在那之前，自从你离开后就一直是这样
but before that it's been like this ever since you left
你在生妈妈的气
You're mad at mom
但你也没在我身边
But you haven't been around either
我不像她
I'm not like her
好吧
Okay
我没有疯
I'm not crazy
是的，你说得对
Yeah , you're right
你没疯
You're not crazy
你根本不在乎
you just don't care
我厌倦了我的女人
I was tired of my lady
我们在一起才知道
we've been together to know
在我的记忆中，这是一个有趣的故事
like a one i recall it of a funter and s
我穿比较好
It's better on m
如果你喜欢我生态得到落在雨中
If you like me ecoloa get fall in the rain
如果你不在这个地方
If you're not in the hoarif
你有一个嘿
You had a hey there
她是
she is
很高兴你来了
So glad you made it
你们是第一位的
You guys actually come first
嘿，大家，过来，过来
hey everybody , come on come on over
做饼干
Made cookies
这是伟大的
it's great
当然可以
Yes of course
你想杀我弟弟吗
Are you trying to kill my brother
哦，我的上帝，上帝是不合逻辑的
Oh my god god is illogic
是的
Yeah
我完全忘了我很抱歉
I totally forgot i'm so sorry
重要的是你在这里
The important thing is that you're here
鲍比酒保到处喝酒
so , uh , bobby bartender drinks drinks all around
你不能选择你得到的
You don't get to pick the one you get
只要爱你现在拥有的
just gotta love the one that you got
现在
Now
我们的母亲直到去世那天都是孤身一人
uh , our mother showed alone till the day that she died
她的死应该提醒你们所有人
And her death should be reminded to all of u
享受生活，共度我们在一起的时光
To enjoy life and spend the time that we have together
这些东西是回不去的
Those are not gonna get any back
我爱你们
I love you guys
哈!你好，车在那儿
Ha ! hi car there
是的
Yeah
欢呼起来
Cheers up
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha
这是不对的，爸爸把它放在那里了
Um , it's wrong fei just put it there
哦,茱莉亚
Oh julia
哦,酷
Oh cool
你已经准备好了
Are you already
天啊，里面有只虫子。哦,我
Oh my god , there's a bug in there . oh i
哦，你懂的，我不认为你懂
Oh you got it i don't think you got it
哦，它是随附的
oh it's coming with
事实上，我正在把关爱变成一份工作
Actually i'm turning love caring jo
太好了，查理
that's great yeah charlie glob
哈哈哈，妈妈，女孩们准备好了
ha ha ha ha mom girls ready
如果我和你一起看呢
What if i join you see bload off
哇
Wow
开始吧
Here we go
你在这里布置得很好
It's great to setup you've got here
我希望孩子们有一个快乐的童年
Well i wanted the kids to have a happy childhood
不像我认识的一些人
Unlike some people i know
哈哈哈，你不是在说这个吧
Ha ha ha you're not talking about that
所以，哦不，我们有一个美好的童年
So yeah , oh no , we had a great childhood
你看着我。我发现
you look at me . i turned out
霍华德
howard
好吧，那是什么
Well , on what is that
但它看起来像一个室内提示
But it looks like a house cue
别这样，我们还有空房间
Come on , you know , we got the spare room
总比在拖车公园里跳来跳去好
and it's gotta be better than bounce around trailer parks
我觉得这不是个好主意
I don't think this is a good idea
第二次机会永远不会太迟
it's never too late for a second chance
我很抱歉
i'm sorry
没有我他们过得更好
they better off without me
接电话接电话
Pick up pick u
来吧，回到我身边，我
come on you back to me i
嘿，爸爸给她看回程
Hey dad shows her back fligh
不，不，不，明天是我的霍华德
no no no yeah tomorrow blower it's my howard
哦，接得好，接得好
Oh nice catch and de okay
好了，开始吧
all right here we go
好吧，爸爸让你做了
Okay dad let you do it
也要远离那一天
stay away from that day as well
在你走之前我还有一个小时
i got hour before you go just like co
我很高兴你决定来
i'm glad you decided to come
全家人都来了
Got the whole family here
哦，嗬，嗬，嗬，耶，好
Oh ho ho ho yeah oka
所有对吗
All righ
哦好
oh good
啊啊啊啊
Ah oh a
我很好，是0
I'm ok it's o
对不起，哇，哇，哇
hsorry wow wow wo
以前的事都过去了
The former things are passed away
既不会有清晨，也不会有痛苦
Neither shall there be morning nor pain
他要擦去
And he shall wipe awa
他们眼中的每一滴眼泪
Every tear from their eyes
死亡将不复存在
And death shall be no more
这些都是什么
what is all this stuff
我在爱尔兰的书里找到了这些文件
I found these papers in irish's book
它们是给人民的讣告和文章
they are obituaries and and articles for the people
是谁在那天晚上看到了天空，虹膜有了预感
Who were at the sky view on the night that iris had a premonition
这些人都以奇怪而混乱的方式死去了
Each one of these people went on to die in in some weird and messed up way
不仅如此，他们的死亡顺序和虹膜的预感一致
And and not only that , they all died in the same orders as iris is premonition
数百人本该在那晚死去
Hundreds of people were supposed to die that night
但我阻止了这场灾难
But i was i was stopped the disaster
于是死神一个接一个地回来了
So death came back for them one by one
因为有这么多幸存者
Since there were so many survivors
过了很多年，死亡才降临到他们身上
It took years for death to get to all of them
但最终它变成了虹膜
But eventually it got to iris
在预感中，她是最后一个死去的
She was last to die in the premonition
是她和一个小男孩
it was her and and a little boy it
但她准备好了
But she was prepared
她凭一己之力抵挡了几十年的死亡
She single handedly held off death for for decades
叶德娴亲爱的
Deanie sweetie
我觉得现在对我们来说不太合适
I don't think this is the appropriate time with us
是的
Yeah
我的意思是这些都和这个没有任何关系，对吧
I mean none of this even has anything to do with this , right
为什么是我们？不，就是这样它和这件事有很大关系
Why are we ? no , that's it that it has everything to do with this
我的意思是
I mean bi
因为死亡需要很长时间才能穿过幸存者
Because death took so long to make its way through the survivors
这些人后来都有了家庭
These people went on to have families
他们本不该拥有的家庭
Families that they never should have had
所以死亡也带走了他们
So death took them too
噢,是的
Oh yeah
是的
Yeah
难道你看不出死亡正在向你袭来吗
Don't you see this death is coming for u
因为我们不应该存在
Because we were never supposed to exist
好吧，为什么这个房间里的每个人都在听那首歌呢
Ok , so why everybody in this room is on that's hitless bobby
住手，她是这么说的
Stop that's what she said
不，不，爸爸和阿姆布伦达很安全
No , no , dad and ambrenda are saf
因为他们不是我的血脉
Because they're not part of ire's bloodline
好吧
Okay
遵循以下模式
Following the pattern
随着年龄的增长，死亡沿着每根树枝向下延伸
Death makes its way down each branch by age
因为霍华德叔叔是老大
So because uncle howard was the oldest
首先从他的家人开始，也就是埃里克
It'll start with his family first meaning eric
下一个是你，去死吧
You're next go fuck yourself
然后它会去找茱莉亚
Then it'll go for julia
然后鲍比
Then bobby
然后它会来我们的分支，从tharene开始
Then it will come for our branch , starting with tharene
然后我
Then me
然后查尔梅
Then charme
查理
Charlie
你相信吗？
You buying this
哦,不
Oh no
这太棒了
This is so master
我是说你把我们爸爸的死变成了某种该死的阴谋论
I mean you're turning our dad's death into some kind of fucked up conspiracy theory
什么是生的，不，不，不，不，不，不
What is raw with no , no , no , no , no , no
这不是这也不是阴谋
It's not it's not a conspiracy too
我们都要下水了
And that we're all gonna dip
停!我一分钟都听不下去了
Stop ! i can't listen to this for one more minute
那个疯女人的胡言乱语已经给这个家庭带来了足够的痛苦
That crazy woman's nonsense has cause enough pain suffering for this family
Pm和renda，请不要打扰我
Pm and renda , please leave me alone
好吧
Okay
在艾弗的书里，她提到了一个逃过死亡的人
In in iver's book she mentioned somebody who cheated deaths and survived
一步。
Step
来吧。埃里克，不，等等
Come on . eric , no , wait
我很担心你
I'm worried about you